{
	"gerund4": [
    {
      "question": "She makes a point of ___ to him once a week.",
      "a": "writing",
      "b": "having written",
      "c": "being written",
      "d": "having been written",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Make a point of + V_ing: To be sure of doing it or take care to do it \n- Verb tense: Simple tense, active voice",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "J. F.Kennedy liked ___ many questions at the press conference.",
      "a": "being asked",
      "b": "asking",
      "c": "of asking",
      "d": "ask",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- Like + V_ing\n\n- Verb form: passive voice",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "It goes without ___ that Isaac Stern is among the greatest violinists.",
      "a": "saying",
      "b": "say",
      "c": "to say",
      "d": "to have said",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- Without + V_ing",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "She is very busy ___ for a journey.",
      "a": "to prepare",
      "b": "preparing",
      "c": "to be preparing",
      "d": "being prepared",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Be busy + V_ing",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "He went ___ in the river nearby.",
      "a": "fish",
      "b": "fishing",
      "c": "to fishing",
      "d": "having fish",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- Go + V-ing: Name of a sport\n\nEx: Go fishing, go jogging",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "___ one's work properly may be worse than not doing it at all.",
      "a": "Not do",
      "b": "Do",
      "c": "Not doing",
      "d": "Doing",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- We use V-ing clause to play as the subject of the sentence",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The one job my husband does not like is ___.",
      "a": "to taking out the garbage",
      "b": "taking out the garbage",
      "c": "to be taking out the garbage",
      "d": "out taking the garbage",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- We used V-ing clause to give more explanation to other action",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "She didn't seem to mind ___ TV while she was trying to study.",
      "a": "their watching",
      "b": "them to watch",
      "c": "their watch",
      "d": "for them to watch",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- Verb (mind, dislike, resent, object, excuse, forgive, pardon, prevent) + possessive adjective/ pronoun + V-ing\"",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jennifer said in her letter that she'd anticipate ___ from you some time.",
      "a": "to hear",
      "b": "hearing",
      "c": "having heard",
      "d": "to hearing",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- Anticipate + V_ing\n\n- Verb form: simple past tense",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Mark, scolded by his teacher, finally confessed to ___ the book.",
      "a": "have stolen",
      "b": "steal",
      "c": "stealing",
      "d": "having stolen",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Some Verbs followed by To + V_ing \n- Ex: Confess to V_ing, Looking forward to V_ing \n- Verb tense: Present perfect",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "42",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}